<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on IoThings</title>
    <link>https://iothings.fr/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on IoThings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 07:27:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iothings.fr/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Locations</title>
      <link>https://iothings.fr/features/locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 07:27:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iothings.fr/features/locations/</guid>
      <description>With IoThings, you can manage different sources of locations.
GPS Locations You can send a location
Wifi Locations Sigfox Spot&amp;rsquo;It TDoA Locations This type of location is automatically created with the Spot&amp;rsquo;it service, and it&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Sigfox Callback, that will send you coarse locations (based on TDoA: Time Difference of Arrival of Sigfox Signals).
In short, this will allow you to have a point and an estimation of where your object is within a radius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Messages</title>
      <link>https://iothings.fr/features/messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 07:16:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iothings.fr/features/messages/</guid>
      <description>Messages With IoThings, your messages can arrive from different types of objects. You can choose to store raw data (for example for a BLE device), or structured data with metadatas (for example for Sigfox devices).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Users and things management</title>
      <link>https://iothings.fr/features/users-things-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 05:34:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iothings.fr/features/users-things-management/</guid>
      <description>Users management With IoThings, a major part of user management is already done. For exemple, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at a classical user journey.
When a user registers to your platform, he is stored in your database, and receives a mail with a link to activate it&amp;rsquo;s account.
&amp;ndash;
Things management With IoThings, you can have a complete management of your objects. Your devices are groupped into fleets, and you can create, delete and manage them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>